Hey Yudoha
You can't answer the phone
Where did you go
It seems like it's not where I expected it to be.
A customer of the cafe has been there
I guess
It seems like we're together
So where do you go?
sea
Why is my phone in the sea?
I told you not to touch my child.
Because it's not accurate yet
Let’s calm down some of the anger.
Then what about the company now?
Can I do this now?
Oh that's it
I'll take care of it
Please hurry up
Hey Yu Dong-ah
uh
how are you here
you are crazy
I told you to answer the phone
You were worried.
I lost my phone
What
When I got here, it wasn't there.
stop
It's okay
Ah
It's okay, no, I'm not okay, bro.
No, can a player hit someone?
So I
I told you not to touch it.
no what am i
I think he might have made a wreath on Do-hyeong.
This is the real Lee
Why are you trying to hit something again?
Let’s eat first.
Ah, but how can we do it together?
Ah
That's a bit long to explain.
I couldn't contact you so I went to see you.
No way, come here
yes
Ah
why are you smiling
Hey, are you on your phone now?
Do you still smile like that even after losing it?
you are here
Then there is no problem going home.
You can report the loss tomorrow.
Let’s eat first. Okay, the phone is
Because you come back again
don't worry
Let’s eat some first, bro.
It was fun today
Who did you run away from?
ha
Ah
Still, I received it like this
cool and nice
I should come here often
to see the sea
Was it very difficult?
Oh no, it's not like that.
I was just a little frustrated.
The company is like that too
The interview results aren't out yet.
Like this and that
Everything will be fine
I do whatever I want
Because Doha shines
uh
brother
This isn't your cell phone.
uh my phone
thank you
I guess I fell while walking here earlier.
Still, I'm glad I found it.
thank you
Are you tired from driving?
It's okay
You must be tired, so go in quickly.
But what about motorcycles?
It's okay bro
Delivery will come tomorrow
Don't worry
Anyway
Thank you for your hard work today
yes
Then let's go
Then bro
Don't worry and sleep well today
I'm going
Then I'll just go too.
Now
Hey, today
You might be tired, but take a rest first.
Let's talk tomorrow
Go in
Hey Yu Dong-ah
I told you to answer the phone
You were worried.
Still, I received it like this
cool and nice
I should come here often
To receive it
If it was really an accident
If it's because you're drunk like you said
Why do I need time?
I don't want you eating with just anyone.
Last unpleasant incident
You organized it well. Oh, of course.
It's just one temple.
Hahahaha
This time until the end
Please take care of me
Oh yes I understand
don't worry
yes
Let's hear some explanation.
yes let's start
Ah ah
Ah
It's so okay
I'm surprised
Oh my
Just look at the love letter. Why are you so surprised?
Oh my oh my
Ah, this is when you were in high school.
Wow, you were cute just then.
Well mom, not now.
Oh my, now I’m all grown up and it’s disgusting
I made peace with my dog.
I've never fought
I didn't do it. I didn't do it.
Ugh
I don't know what it is, but this time you go first
Please lose once
Dog always came first.
Look at everything
eat
Hey, be careful, be careful, be careful
hey i won
I can't give it to you
It's ours
I want to eat chocolate
Hey, you come early
do
Turn around
Going
This
work
Ding
I'm sorry
I think it will be difficult
Hello
code red
Between us, we call it code red
Speaking of code red
Come running right away
It's a kind of danger signal.
Hey Yu Dong-ah
You're okay, Yoo Dong-ah.
I told you to answer the phone
You were worried.
Judo
let's go
Hey
Hey hey
no
I cry so much over something like this
I didn't even get hurt once or twice
So
Don't get hurt
I'm okay
As if it never happened
I can't do it
uh
first kiss
No matter how bad it is
I like it
Taekkyeon
Please say something
Yudoah
Those words cannot be undone.
We're not friends anymore
danger detection signal
Yudoah
Godrad